A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 8, Accession 8 FA1190
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Board of Directors, Committees, and Members records, 1958, 1965-2014; 11
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (K), Still Image (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Koshland, Daniel E.), 1958; 1966-1979; Still Image (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (L) (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Lockwood, William Wirt), 1970-1979 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (M-N ) (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (O-Q) (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (O'Neal, Frederick), 1970-1992 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased - R (Box 9, Folder 34)
    Includes Edwin Reischauer, 1966-1990.
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (S) (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Sebes, Joseph S., S. J.), 1967-1990 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    Includes color portrait photo (snapshot).
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Seligman, Eustace, and Maud J. Seligman), 1966-1982 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Stanley, C. Maxwell), 1967-1984 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (T) (Box 9, Folder 39)
    Includes Cecil Thomas.
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (U-Z) (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Former Members Files: Deceased (Yost, Charles), 1968-1981 (Box 10, Folder 41-42)
    Includes 4 x 6 black and white portrait photo of Yost.
  - Former Members: Aaron, Daniel, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Former Members: Abati, Alfred, 2003-2007 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Former Members: Abboud, A. Robert, 1973-1985 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Former Members: Abramowitz, Morton, 1993-2003 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Former Members: Abramson, G. Patricia, 1980-1989 (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Former Members: Adams, Ruth, 1970-2002 (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Former Members: Ahl, George W., Jr., 1991-2002 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Former Members: Ahmanson, Caroline L., 1973-2005 (Box 10, Folder 50-51)
  - Former Members: Alford - Amory (Box 10, Folder 52)
    Alford, William P., 1992; Alitto, Guy, 1981-1985, 2002; Allen, Marvell, 1993-2003; Allen, Yorke, Jr., 1978-1987; Allison, John M., 1967-1978; Amory, Thomas C., 1980-1989.
  - Former Members: Anderson - Armstrong (Box 10, Folder 53)
    Anderson, Eugenie, 1974-1985; Anderson, James B., 1971-1982; Anderson, Robert B., 2003; Anderson, Robert O., 1973-1989; Anderson, William S., 1974-1997; Andreasen, Andrew J., 1977-1991; Armstrong, Robert E., 1984-1989.
  - Former Members: Ashdown - Attwood (Box 10, Folder 54)
    Ashdown, Marie M., 1989; Ashmore, Harry, 1967-1982; Atherton, Holt, 1979-1985; Atkin, J. Myron, 1979-1989; Atkinson, Harry W., 1974-1985; Atkinson, Thomas M., 1989-1997; Attwood, William, 1971-1989.
  - Former Members: Avery - Aylward (Box 10, Folder 55)
    Avery, R. Stanton, 1983-1985; Ayers, Thomas G., 1983-1985; Ayers, Thomas W. (Bill), 1982-1987; Aylward, Robert A., 1974-1985.
  - Former Members: Bailey - Baker (Box 11, Folder 56)
    Bailey, Charles W. and Ann C., 1974-2010; Baker, Michael H., 1978-1997 (resigned).
  - Former Members: Balis - Bargoorn (Box 11, Folder 57)
    Balis, C. Wanton, 1974-1985; Bane, Charles A., 1966-1971, 1985; Bannister, Judith, 1997-2002; Barbey, Grace Holmes, 1976-1990; Barghoorn, Frederick C., 1967, 1978.
  - Former Members: Barnett, A. Doak, 1965-1999; 2002 (Box 11, Folder 58-61)
    File includes January 1969 memo on Membership policy and board leadership.
  - Former Members: Barnett, Jeanne B., and A. Doak Barnett, 1980-1998 (Box 11, Folder 62)
    File also includes acknowlegements of joint contributions from A. Doak and Jeanne B. Barnett.
  - Former Members: Barnett - Beemer (Box 12, Folder 63)
    Barnett, Eugene E. (father of A. Doak Barnett), 1966-1968; Barnett, Robert W., 1972-1992; Baron, Barnett F., 1997-1998; Becker, Irving H., 1978-1985, 2002; Beckmann, George M., 1971-1989; Beebe, George A., 1965-1968, 1982-1997 (deceased 1992); Beemer, Halsey L., Jr., 1983-1992.
  - Former Members: Behrens - Bellamy (Box 12, Folder 64)
    Behrens, Bernice W., 1981-1992; Beirne, Joseph A., 1971; Bell, Colin, 1964-1968, 1978; Bell, Daniel, 1971; Bell, Peter D., 1988-2002; Bellamy, Carol, 1979-1999.
  - Former Members: Bemiss - Benjamin (Box 12, Folder 65)
    Bemiss, FitzGerald, 1975-1985; Benet, Sarah L., 1973, 1976; Benbow, John R., 1973-1977; Beningson, Susan, 1999; Benjamin, Jean K. (Mrs. Robert S.), 1970-1984; Benjamin, Robert S., 1967-1978
  - Former Members: Bennett, Gordon, 1973-1995 (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Former Members: Bennett, Louise, 1971-1978 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Former Members: Bennett, Richard K., 1969-1988 (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Former Members: Benton - Bernstein (Box 12, Folder 69)
    Benton, Charles, 1972-1997; Beplat, Tristan E., 1972-2006; Bergendoff, Conrad, 1974-1976; Berliner, Sanford A., 1992-2002; Bernstein, Robert L., 1992-2004
  - Former Members: Besser, Albert G., 1978-2002 (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Former Members: Bildner - Bishop (Box 12, Folder 71)
    Bildner, Albert, 1979-2003; Bilheimer, Robert S., 1968-1997; Binder, Frederick M., 1990; Bingham, Woodbridge, 1967-1985; Bishop, Max W. S., 1968-1975.
  - Former Members: Black - Blinder (Box 12, Folder 72)
    Black, Craig, 1982-1985; Blackwelder, Brent, 1990; Blake, Robert O., 1990; Blatchford, Charles H., 1974-1989; Blinder, Abe L., 1982-1989
  - Former Members: Block - Blumstein (Box 13, Folder 73)
    Block, William, 1970-2005 (deceased); Bloom, Martin, 1996-1997; Bloomer, John W., 1971, 1982-1985; Blum, John A., 1980-1989, 1997; Blumstein, Allan, 2000-2005.
  - Former Members: Boardman - Bodine (Box 13, Folder 74)
    Boardman, Eugene, 1966-1987; Boas, Roger, 1974-1990, 2002; Bobrow, Davis B., 1974-1985; Bodine, William W., Jr., 1974-1983.
  - Former Members: Booker - Boyer (Box 13, Folder 75)
    Booker, W. Wayne, 1995-2000; Boorman, Howard L., 1966-1985; Borg, Dorothy, 1972-1985; Bosrock, Ronald M., 1986-1999; Bowers, John Z., 1971-1976; Bowman, John E., 1973-1981; Boyd, William B., 1988-2002; Boyer, Ernest L, 1990 (deceased).
  - Former Members: Bradley - Brennan (Box 13, Folder 76)
    Bradley, Gail S. (Mrs. David G.), 1972-1977; Brandon, Mabel H. (Mrs. Henry), 1977-1985; Brennan, Martin J., 1972-1985.
  - Former Members: Brick - Brunner (Box 13, Folder 77)
    Brick, Andrew, 1973-1999; Brody, Alexander, 1990-1991, 2002; Brooks, Gladys S., 1974-1996; Brordy, Melvin, 1971-1982; Brouillet, Frank B., 1982-1994; Brown, Harrison, 1971-1985; Brown, Jane Smyth, 1979-1989; Brown, Norman L., 1991; Brunner, Michael A., 1992-2002.
  - Former Members: Franklin R. Buchanan, 1970-1982; 2003 (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Former Members: Buchman - Bush (Box 13, Folder 79)
    Buchman, Mark E., 1984; Bundy, William P., 1971-1990; Burgess, Carter L., 1976-1985; Burke, Fred G., 1980-1992; Burke, Michael, 1977-1981; Burkhardt, Frederick, 1971-1991; Bush, Walker, 1978-1982.
  - Former Members: Buss, Claude A., 1966-1997 (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Former Members: Buttenweiser, Benjamin J., 1966-1973 (Box 13, Folder 81)
    Resigned.
  - Former Members: Cahill - Cameron (Box 13, Folder 82)
    Cahill, James, 1973-1985; Calhoun, Alexander, 1973-1988; Cameron, Catherine, 1983-2006
  - Former Members: Cameron, Alison Stilwell, 1973-1992 (Box 14, Folder 83)
    Daughter of Gen. Joseph W. Stilwell.
  - Former Members: Camp - Carter (Box 14, Folder 84)
    Camp, Carolyn Passonneau, 1973-1974 (deceased 1975); Campbell, Colin G., 1990, 1998; Canham, Erwin D., 1968-1978; Carlson, Allen R., 2002-2006; Carpenter, M. Kathleen, 1981-1991; Carrick, Emmaline Hardy, 1982-1985; Carrozza, Vincent A., 1967-1987 (resigned); Carter, Don E., 1974-1987; Carter, Hodding, III, 1968-1985, 2002; Carter, Margaret, 1974-1977.
  - Former Members: Cartwright - Carver (Box 14, Folder 85)
    Cartwright, Betty Goff Cook, 1978-2005; Carver, Richard, 1982-1990.
  - Former Members: Case, Everett, 1966-1994; 2002 (Box 14, Folder 86-87)
  - Former Members: Castile - Chang (Box 14, Folder 88)
    Castile, Rand, 1991-2002; Catanzaro, Jeffrey, 2003; Chai, W. Alvin, 1986-1989; Chai, Winberg, 1987; Chan, James W., 1996, 2002; Chan, Lo-Yi, 1991-2002; Chandler, William U., 1992-2002; Chaney, Leo V., Jr., 2003; Chang, C. Y., 1984-1989; Chang, David P. C., 1979-1991, 2002; Chang, Gordon H., 1992-2002; Chang, Wayne Thomas, 1995-1996.
  - Former Members: Chapin - Chen (Box 14, Folder 89)
    Chapin, Schuyler G., 1978-1989; Chaplin, George, 1974-1985; Char, Kenneth, 1981-1988; Chatfield-Taylor, Adele, 1981-1989; Cheek, Timothy C., 1992-2000; Chen, Chung-min, 1989; Chen, Clement, Jr., 1974-1988.
  - Cheng - Choi (Box 15, Folder 90)
    Cheng, Hang-Sheng, 1992-2008; Cheng, J. Chester, 1984-2004; Cheng, Lucie, 1984-2002; Cheng, Tsung O., M.D., 1979-2008; Chernoff, Howard L., 1976-1987; Chiao, Lungching, 1992, 2002; Ching, Bob L. S., 1992-2002; Cho, Lee-Jay, 1992-1993; Choi, Christopher, 1990.
  - Chou, Wen-chung, 1973-1993 (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Former Members: Chow - Clement (Box 15, Folder 92)
    Chow, Edward C., 2001-2002; Chow, Peter C. Y., 2001-2002; Christopher, Robert C., 1971-1985; Chu, Lynn T., 1991, 2002; Churchill, Buntzie Ellis, 1974-1985; Clark, Merrell E., Jr., 1979-1985; Clark, Richard, 1990-1991, 2002; Clark, William, Jr., 2001-2002; Clement, Norman P., Jr., 1976-2003
  - Former Members: Cleveland, Harlan, 1971-1989 (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Former Members: Cleveland, Robert - Collinsworth (Box 15, Folder 94)
    Cleveland, Robert G., 1975-2002; Clough, Ralph N., 1973-1989, 2007; Coblentz, William K., 1966-1990; Codding, Judy, 1980-1985; Cohen, David, 1978-2002; Cohen, Warren I., 1979-1996; Cole, Bruce A., 1997; Coliver, Edith, 1973-2000; Collins, H. Thomas, 1973-1980; Collinsworth, Even T., 1974-1978.
  - Former Members: Conable, Barber B., 1992-2003 (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Former Members: Console - Corcoran (Box 15, Folder 96)
    Console, Edward T., 1984-1985; Cook, Ransom, 1966-1978; Cooper, Richard V. L., 1986-1992; Corcoran, Patrick, 2004-2005.
  - Former Members: Corn, Edward, 1982-1997; Still Image: 3.5 x 7 color print. (Box 15, Folder 97)
    Corn died in 1997. File includes photograph of Corn's wife and daughter (birth announcement).
  - Former Members: Corson - Coyne, Herbert J. (Box 15, Folder 98)
    Corson, William R., 1983-2000; Coudert, Dale, 1986-1987; Coursen, Richard Dennison, 1986-1989; Cowles, John, 1968-1975; Coyne, Herbert J., 1991-1997.
  - Former Members: Coyne, Marshall B., 1980-2000 (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - Former Members: Craighill - Cutchin (Box 16, Folder 100)
    Craighill, Francis H., III, 1978-1985; Cronk, Dennis R. 2000; Crook, Frederick W., 2003-2005; Cross, Charles T., 1988-2008 (deceased); Crowley, Ellen, 1982-1985; Crowley, Patricia C. (Mrs. Patrick F.), 1973-1984, 2005 (deceased); Crowley, Philip J., 2001-2003; Curley, Walter J. P., 1978-1989; Cutchin, Virginia L., 2003.
  - Former Members: Darby - de Lima (Box 16, Folder 101)
    Darby, Mary Wadsworth, 1990-2000; David, Bryna Ball (Mrs. Henry), 1985; David, Henry, 1972-1984; de Bary, William Theodore, 1972-1985; de Keijzer, Arne J., 1976-2002; de Kleven, Concha Ortiz y Pino, 1978-1985; de Lima, Oscar A., 1969-1985.
  - Former Members: Delano, William A., 1969-2004; Still Images: two 4x6 color prints, one attached to 8.5 x 11 sheet of paper. (Box 16, Folder 102-103)
    Folder 103 includes snapshot of Delano (and wife?), and group photo of the Board of Directors Delegation, November 1982.
  - Former Members: DeMuth, Christopher (Box 16, Folder 104)
    DeMuth, Christopher, 1988-2002; Dennis, Joseph R., 1995-2002; Dennison, Charles S., 1966-1984; Derbes, Daniel W., Dernberger, Robert F., 1984-2003; DeWoskin, Kenneth J., 1986-1997; Dick, Edison W., 1986-2002; Dickerson, Earl B., 1971-1985; Diddel, Katha, 1992-2005, 2014.
  - Former Members: Diebold, John, 1969-1989; Still Image: black and white 8x10 print (Box 16, Folder 105-106)
    Includes black and white 8x10 portrait photo of Diebold.
  - Former Members: Diebold, John, 1990-2005 (Box 17, Folder 107)
  - Former Members: Diebold, John (Biographical File), circa 1971 - 1985 (Box 17, Folder 108)
  - Former Members: Dien - Ditmore (Box 17, Folder 109)
    Dien, Albert E., 1978-2006; DiGiorgio, Patricia K., 1973-1990; Dillard, Annie, 1983-1989; Dills, Ralph C., 1984-1989; Dineen, Gerald P., 1985-1986; Ditmore, Michael, 2003
  - Former Members: Dolfin - Driver (Box 17, Folder 110)
    Dolfin, John, 1991-1998; Doty, James T., Drake, William E., 1976-1989; Drasnin, Irv, 1974, 1979-2002; Dreyer, June Teufel, 1990-2001; Driver, W. Nicholas, 2002-2003.
  - Former Members: Dubuc - Dym (Box 17, Folder 111)
    Dubuc, Carroll E., 1991-1997; Dumbaugh, Kerry, 1992-2005; Dunaway, Mac S., 1989; Duncan, Hobert E., 1974-1977; Dyal, William M., Jr., 1984-1991; Dym, Herbert 1982-1985.
  - Former Members: Earle - Edwards (Box 17, Folder 112)
    Earle, Sylvia A., 1981-2002; Easterbrooke, Nancy Stilwell, 1977-1997; Eckstein, Ruth, 1978-2001; Edgerton, Wallace B., 1973-1985; Edwards, R. Randle, 1981-1990.
  - Former Members: Eidenberg - Ellis (Box 17, Folder 113)
    Eidenberg, Eugene, 1996-1998; EisenhowerDwight David, II, 1982-1985; Eisner, Michael D., 1986-1989; Ellis, Jim, 2000
  - Former Members: Elliott, Jeannette Shambaugh, 1973-1996 (Box 17, Folder 114)
  - Former Members: Emmerson - Ewing (Box 17, Folder 115)
    Emmerson, John K., 1973-1974; Enarson, Harold L., 1976-2006 (deceased); Esch, Marvin L., 1984-1985; Evans, James H., 1985-1986; Ewing, Mary Hamilton, 1982-1985.
  - Former Members: Fabrikant - Fiester (Box 17, Folder 116)
  - Former Members: Findley - Firebaugh (Box 18, Folder 117)
    Findley, Paul, 1984-1985; Finkelstein, David M., 1999; Finnell, Robert A., 1983-1985; Firebaugh, Francille M., 1993-1999.
  - Former Members: Fischer, William A., 1984-2006 (Box 18, Folder 118)
  - Former Members: Fleishman - Foerster (Box 18, Folder 119)
    Fleishman, Jack, 1981-1984; Fleming, Robben W., 1967-1997; Fligg, James E., 1995-2002; Fluor, J. Robert, 1974-1984; Foell, Earl W., 1982-2002; Foerster, Bernd, 1984-1997.
  - Former Members: Fong - Ford (Box 18, Folder 120)
    Fong, Lloyd, 1984-1994 (deceased); Force, Robert, 1997 (resigned); Ford, Andrew T., 1986-2002; Ford, President Gerald R., 1981-2006; Ford, Paul B., Jr., 1986, 1989.
  - Former Members: Forrestal - Fox (Box 18, Folder 121)
    Forrestal, Michael V., 1969-1989; Foster, Brenda Lei, 1992-2001; Foster, Charles C., 1990-2005; Foster, Lawrence H., 1983-1985; Fox, Christine H., 2007-2009 (resigned); Fox, George A., 1986-1990; Fox, Joseph C., 1996-1997.
  - Former Members: Frank - Friday, Still Image: Black and white 2.5 x. 3.5 print. (Box 18, Folder 122)
    Frank, Peter B., 1983-1989; Frankenstein, John, 1999-2001; Franklin, John Hope, 1974-1989; Frantz, Terrill L., 1996, 2002; Fravel, M. Taylor, 2004-2005; Frazier, Mark W., 1999-2001; Fredericks, J. Wayne, 1974-1989; Freedman, Robert O., 1991-1994; Freeman, Jerre Minor, 1990-1992, 2002; Frevert, Peter, 1991; Frick, Harry D., III, 2004 (includes portrait photo); Friday, William, 1974-1985.
  - Former Members: Friedman, Edward, 1970-1997 (Box 18, Folder 123)
  - Former Members: Friedman, Robert - Fromson (Box 18, Folder 124)
    Friedman, Robert, 2004-2006; Friendly, Fred W., 1972-1985; Fromson, Murray, 1978-1985
  - Former Members: Gadsden - Gayner (Box 18, Folder 125)
    Gadsden, Amy E., 2000-2005; Gaffney, Elizabeth, 2005-2006; Galgiani, Phoebe, 1978-1985; Galston, Arthur W., 1972-1991; Garfinkel, Gloria, 1982, 2002; Garrett, Banning, 1998; Gates, Philomene A., 1980-2006; Gaudion, Donald A., 1972-1985; Gayner, Jeffrey B., 1984-1995.
  - Former Members: Gelb - Gittelman (Box 18, Folder 126)
    Gelb, Leslie H., 1999-2003; Genoves, Roberto, 2005; Geppert, Otto Emil, 1968-1969; Gerstley, James M., 1973-1985; Gettelfinger, Thomas C., 1990-2002; Geyer, Robert B., 1992; Giacomo, Carol A., 2001-2002; Giancarlo, Gene, 1974-1983; Gibney, Frank B., 1998-2006; Gifford, Karen K., 1983-1987; Ginsburg, Norton S., 1973-1996; Gittleman, Martin, 1992, 1999.
  - Former Members: Glaser - Golden (Box 19, Folder 127)
    Glaser, Bonnie S., 1997-2004; Gleysteen, William H., Jr., 1982-2002; Goheen, Robert F., 1969-1996; Goldberg, Arthur J., 1969-1973; Goldberg, Harry, 1968-1973; Goldberg, Marshall, 2004; Golden, James R., 1980-1985; Golden, Mrs. William T. (Sibyl L.), 1971-1984.
  - Former Members: Goldstein - Gong (Box 19, Folder 128)
    Goldstein, Harold K., 2004; Goldstein, Melvyn C., 1997-2002; Goldstein, Steven M., 1983-2001; Gomperts, Robert E., 1973-1985; Gong, Gerrit W., 1992-2002.
  - Former Members: Good - Greathead (Box 19, Folder 129)
    Good, Roert C., 1973-1985; Goodlad, John, 1999; Goodman, Rita, 1978-2000; Gordon, Beate, 1984-1989; Gorman, Paul R., 1991-1997 (deceased); Gossett, William T., 1972-1982; Gottlieb, Sanford, 2000-2001; Gould, Samuel, 1971-1974; Graham, Patricia Albjerg, 1979-2002; Graham, William R., 1992-1993, 1989; Grant, James P., 1972-1995 (deceased); Gray, Sherry, 1994, 2002; Greathead, R. Scott, 2002.
  - Former Members: Green, Marshall, 1981-1999 (Box 19, Folder 130)
  - Former Members: Greenfield - Guyer (Box 19, Folder 131)
    Greenfield, James L., 1985-1989; Greenwald, Joseph A., 1994-1997 (resigned); Gregg, Dorothy E., 1979-1989; Grimes, Charlotte, 1997-2002; Gross, Ernest A., 1967-1985; Grossman, Ann M., 1999-2004 (also includes Stephen L. Grossman); Gurtov, Melvin, 1974-2002; Guth, John H. J., 1993; Guthrie, Doug, 2003; Guyer, David L., 1966-1974.
  - Former Members: Halaby, Najeeb E., 1969-2002 (Box 19, Folder 132)
  - Former Members: Hall, McClellan, 1996-2006 (Box 19, Folder 133)
  - Former Members: Halpern - Hanson (Box 19, Folder 134)
    Halpern, Nathan L., 1981-1997; Halpern, Nina, 1988-1993; Hamilton, Randy H., 1978-1999, 2007 (deceased); Hand, Keith J., 2005-2006; Hanson, Robert A., 1974-1990.
  - Former Members: Haratunian, M. William (Box 20, Folder 135)
    Haratunian, M. William, 1984-1989; Hardy, T. Walter, Jr., 1968-1985; Harlis, John Boothroyd, 1993-1997; Harned, David Bailey, 1982-1989; Harpole, Sally A., 1987-2003; Harris, Irving B., 1968-1989; Harrison, James P., 1976-1993; Harrison, Selig S., 1982-1985; Hartman, Arthur A. 1989-2002; Hatch, George C., Jr., 1974-1985; Hatch, Sinclair, 1978-1982; Hawke, Frank, 1996; Hayden, Rose L., 1988-1996; Hayes, George Stephen, 1988-1989.
  - Former Members: Height - Hemphill (Box 20, Folder 136)
    Height, Dorothy L., 1970-1985; Heilbron, Louis H., 1966-2003; Heires, John Hopkins, 1982-1985; Heller, Clarence E., 1966-1985; Hemphill, Bernice M., 1973-1996, 1998.
  - Former Members: Henderson - Hero (Box 20, Folder 137)
    Henderson, Jay, 1989-1990; Henderson, William, 1967-1985; Hendricks, Darryl, 2003-2006; Herndon, Terry, 1973-1985; Hero, Alfred O., Jr., 1967-1985.
  - Former Members: Hesburgh, CSC, Theodore M., 1967-2002 (Box 20, Folder 138)
  - Former Members: Hess - Heyns (Box 20, Folder 139)
    Hess, Carl B., 1983-1985; Hewitt, Patricia W. (Mrs. William A.), 1973-1985; Heyns, Roger W., 1968-1993.
  - Former Members: Higgins - Ho (Box 20, Folder 140)
    Higgins, Msgr. George G., 1966-1985; Hilborn, Walter, 1971; Hinton, Carma, 1996-2003; Hinton, Harold C., 1967-1993; Ho, James K., 1992-2002; Ho, Nelson C., 1993-2006; Ho, Ping-ti, 1973-1975 (resigned)
  - Former Members: Hofheinz - Holdridge (Box 20, Folder 141)
    Hofheinz, Roy, Jr., 1971-1985; Holcombe, Arthur N., 1967-1974 (resigned); Holden, Reuben A., 1972-1978; Holdridge, John H., 1986-2001.
  - Former Members: Holland - Holober, Still Image: Black and white 5x7 print (Box 20, Folder 142)
    Holland, Kenneth, 1976; Hollis, Everett L., 1972-1989; Holmes, Robert A., 1974-1985 (includes portrait photo); Holober, Frank, 1983-2003.
  - Former Members: Hoose - House, Still Image: Black and white 4x5 print (Box 21, Folder 143)
    Hoose, Georgia Johnston (Mrs. Harned Pettus), 1976-1985; Hoose, Harned Pettus, 1972-1977, 1982 (includes portrait photo; also includes Georgia Hoose); Hoston, Germaine A., 1992; House, Karen Elliott, 1997-1998.
  - Former Members: Hsieh - Hsu (Box 21, Folder 144)
    Hsieh, Chiao-min, 1982-1985; Hsu, Francis L. K., 1972-1985, 2002; Hsu, F. Richard, 1972-1985, 1991; Hsu, Mei-ling, 1981-2005
  - Former Members: Hsueh, Chun-tu, 1976-2006; Still Images: 2 black and white 5x7 prints (Box 21, Folder 145-146)
    Folder 145 includes two images of Hsueh with Ye Jianying and with Deng Xiaoping, October 1981.
  - Former Members: Hu, C.T. (Ch'ang-tu), 1973-1985; 2002 (Box 21, Folder 147)
  - Former Members: Hughes - Hunt (Box 21, Folder 148)
    Hughes, Lyric, 2001-2005; Hughes, Thomas L., 1976-1991; Hummel, Arthur W., Jr., 1986-2001; Hummel, Betty Lou, 2001-2011; Hunt, James C., 2003; Hunt, Michael B., 1992-2002.
  - Former Members: Hunter, David R., 1966-1998; 2007 (Box 21, Folder 149)
  - Former Members: Hurd - Hyman (Box 21, Folder 150)
    Hurd, Paul DeHart, 1981-1989; Hurst, Mary Ann, 1990-2003; Hutar, Patricia, 1979-1988; Huth, Arno, 1983-1985; Hyman, Sadie (Mrs. George), 1968-1977
  - Former Members: Ilchman - Israel (Box 21, Folder 151)
    Ilchman, Alice Stone, 1981-1987; Ipson, Michael K., 1990-2002; Irani, Ray R., 1990-1994; Israel, John, 1974-1997.
  - Former Members: Jacobson - Jessup (Box 22, Folder 152)
    Jacobson, Carl W., 1994, 2002; Jamieson, John C., 1978-1992; Jarman, Franklin M., 1975, 1978; Jarrett, James W., 2003-2012 (deceased); Jarrett, Stephen W., 1991-2006; Jefferson, Gary H., 1998, 2001; Jen, Chih-kung, 1978-1995 (deceased); Jennings, Edward H., 1998; Jessup, Alpheus W., 1972-1991.
  - Former Members: Jhin - Joiner (Box 22, Folder 153)
    Jhin, Philip, 1992, 2002; Johnson, Chalmers A., 1967-2002; Johnson, Joseph E., 1965-1975 (resigned); Joiner, Lynne S., 1979-1989.
  - Jones - Joseph (Box 22, Folder 154)
    Jones, Charles O., 1993-2002; Jones, David A., Jr., 1995; Jones, James R., 1997-2002; Jones, Sidney, 2002; Jones, Tracey K., Jr., 1969-1985; Jordan, Amos A., 1994, 2002; Jordan, James D., 1986-2003; Jordan, Vernon E., Jr., 1986-2003; Jorgensen, Russell F. 1974-1982; Joseph, William A., 1973-1997.
  - Former Members: Kagan - Kaplan (Box 22, Folder 155)
    Kagan, Richard C., 1973-1985; Kaiser, Edgar F., 1966-1974; Kalkhurst, Eric T., 1976, 1980; Kamansky, David, 1992; Kamm, Linda Heller, 1980-2002; Kanter, Arnold, 1994-2010; Kaplan, Harold, 1973-1985.
  - Former Members: Karnow - Kau (Box 22, Folder 156)
    Karnow, Stanley, 1971-1990; Katz, Stanley N., 1989-2002; Kau, Michael Ying-mau, 1976-2002
  - Former Members: Keast - Kerr (Box 22, Folder 157)
    Keast, William B., 1982-1985; Keidel, Albert, III, 1989-1993; Keil, Dharmata Kaur (Kathryn), 1992-1997 (resigned); Kelly, John B., Jr., 1974-1975; Kendall, Donald M., 1974-1986; Kendall, John R., 1974-1982; Kerr, Clark, 1966-1997.
  - Former Members: Kessler - Klion (Box 22, Folder 158)
    Kessler, Adam T., 1996, 2001; Keyser, Donald W., 2004; Kilcollin, T. Eric, 1994, 2001; Kincaid, Frank, 2000; Klausner, Michael, 1991; Klion, Stanley R., 1986-1993 (resigned).
  - Former Members: Klutznick, Philip M., 1967-1999 (Box 22, Folder 159)
  - Former Members: Knudson - Krygier (Box 22, Folder 160)
    Knudson, B. Peter, 1974-1980; Komarow, Bruce Allen, 1986-1993; Koo, Rosa, 1990; Koo, Rosalyn, 1978-1982; Korry, Edward M., 1973-1978; Kreisberg, Paul H., 1983-1999; Krygier, Binem, 1971-1974, 1978.
  - Former Members: Kubarych - Kwong (Box 23, Folder 161)
    Kubarych, Roger, 1986-1989; Kuhn, Philip A., 1980-1989; Kupec, William M., 1996-2005; Kutler, Stanley I., 1986-1987; Kuwayama, George, 1989; Kuzmik, John T., 1993-2002; Kwok, Daniel W. Y., 1973-2000; Kwong, Daniel W., 1994-2000.
  - Former Members: LaDier - Larson (Box 23, Folder 162)